jvexecutive.com 2018-06-30

# Up To 75% RECURRING Commissions - Join The Unselfish Marketer's Affiliate Program

**We have a ZERO Spam Policy  

Do you feel one of our affiliates have spammed you, please don't hesitate to use our Support 

If you spam while using our facilities - you're OUT, simple as that! Any loss of Actives is your own fault and any Affiliate Commissions owed are forfeited. I do hope the above was in a clear understandable English

**  **  
Warmest regards,  
**  **  
****JayKay Bak  
JVExecutive.com  
CEO - Unselfish Marketers Co. Ltd.

We Value Your Privacy:  
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our company

Credit Card Details:  
We will never ask for Credit Card details (we use 3rd party secure 128bit encryption companies) and request that you do not enter it on any of our forms

External Sites:  
We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information

Cookies:  
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds

Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet!  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information

In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through us have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies

For any other information please contact us through our Support Below

**

** **** |  JayKay Bak  
**JayKay Bak**  
---|---  
**

**CEO & Founder of The Unselfish Marketers Co. Ltd.**

**All Affiliate Payouts Are Company Guaranteed By Unselfish Marketers Co. Ltd. (Scandinavia)  
Our Postal Address Is: JayKay Bak, Moellevej 4i, 4100 Ringsted, Copenhagen, Denmark.  
Phone: +45 3696 4888 (Office Hours: 1am-9am EST)**
